hi everyone it's a super rainy afternoon
here in tarayande on the city it may be
thinking are we prepared for this kind
of story that kind of stored in life
storms like death in the family critical
illness
accident even a loss of job or even
retirement i'm thinking that and we are
not prepared to retirement
[Music]
those kinds of storms are very difficult
and it really helps if we have a
three-in-one plan that we start
investing and saving for as early as now
if you are healthy it's really the best
time otherwise not having the time
insurable and if you are still capable
of earning love why not start for a
three-in-one policy that can give up my
insurance insurance and pay for that in
the family indeed my health benefits now
you should pay for critical illness or
daily hospitalization but also savings
or investment think of the investment
tobacco if you save in the bank and
something happens
why not invest in a tree in
[Music]
and he was just extremely grateful
managing three in one plan nah
finance nothing savings like emergency
fund so why not have that one and that
savings can be your child's educational
fund it can be your retirement one can
be your
emergency or crisis fund
i hope after watching this video you
will require about this three in the
plan because for sure you will never
regret starting this now thank you very
much